const questions=[
    {
        no: "1",
        question: "What vitamin is needed by the retina of the eye?",
        A: "Vitamin C",
        B: "Vitamin D",
        C: "Vitamin A",
        D: "Vitamin B6",
        answer: "C",
      },
      {
        no: "2",
        question: "What is the name of the diamond shaped muscle in the back that is worked when rowing?",
        A: "Biceps",
        B: "Abdominals",
        C: "Hamstrings",
        D: "Trapezius",
        answer: "D",
      },
      {
        no: "3",
        question: "What type of exercise uses body weight for resistance in a rhythmic manner? ",
        A: "Calisthenics",
        B: "Yoga",
        C: "Pilates",
        D: "Weight Lifting",
        answer: "A",
      },
      {
        no: "4",
        question: "What is hypertrophy?",
        A: "Increasing Muscle Fiber",
        B: "Increasing Calorie Intake",
        C: "Increasing Fat",
        D: "Increasing Your Workout",
        answer: "A",
      },
      {
        no: "5",
        question: "What is it called when your body converts fat into energy?",
        A: "Overtraining",
        B: "Ketosis",
        C: "Hypertrophy",
        D: "Flexibility",
        answer: "B",
      },
      {
        no: "6",
        question: "What does the term anaerobic mean?",
        A: "With oxygen",
        B: "Minimize tissue oxidation",
        C: "Without oxygen",
        D: "Maximize tissue oxidation",
        answer: "C",
      },
      {
        no: "7",
        question: "What term means to eat frequent small amounts of food? ",
        A: "Starving",
        B: "Gorging",
        C: "Binging5",
        D: "Grazing",
        answer: "D",
      },
      {
        no: "8",
        question: "If a leaf falls to the ground in a forest and no one hears it, does it make a sound?",
        A: "Yes",
        B: "No",
        C: "Depends on how heavy the leaf was.",
        D: "Depends on where it landed.",
        answer: "A",
      },
      {
        no: "9",
        question: "There are 45 apples in your basket. You take three apples out of the basket. How many apples are left?",
        A: "3",
        B: "42",
        C: "45",
        D: "I do not eat apple!",
        answer: "C",
      },
      {
        no: "10",
        question: "Mathew's father has three sons- Joseph I and Joseph II. Can you guess the name of the third son?",
        A: "Joseph III",
        B: "Jerin",
        C: "Mathew",
        D: "jenir",
        answer: "A",
      },

];
module.exports=questions;